welcome to the rd.com youtube channel
for travel tips
i'm jonathan breese the ceo and this is
a short video to go along with our blog
article
scenic luxury tours travel insurance a
review
well at ardi.com we can't recommend
travel insurance enough
whether you're traveling just a few
hundred miles to see family
traveling on a business trip or
traveling to the other side of the world
travel insurance should be considered an
essential part of your holiday packing
now the hope is you won't have to use
your travel insurance and that you'll
have a fun
and enjoyable trip the advice in the
blog article should help you make the
most of your trip
and remember we recommend that you
should travel with at least
one hundred thousand dollars of medical
sickness cover
we also recommend that you should have
at least one hundred thousand dollars of
medical evacuation cover as well
and on the screen in front of you you'll
see how quick and easy it is to run a
quote with rd.com
we have many of the top us travel
insurers on our site offering some of
the very finest
travel insurance plans so whether you're
traveling within the us
traveling to europe or heading off on a
cruise we will have the perfect
insurance plan for your
travel needs it'll take you no more than
two minutes to run a quote
and you'll be able to compare and
contrast the products the plans
the prices and the all-important
coverage levels
so that you can make the right buying
decision for your trip and remember
you won't find the same plan cheaper
anywhere else
all travel plans in the us are filed by
state
meaning that no one can sell an
insurance product for a cent more or
less
than that filed price if you do have
any need for assistance our agents are
available
on chat or telephone seven days a week
well wherever you're going whatever
you're doing keep safe and remember to
travel with travel insurance
and do come back and see us again soon
take care
you